Hi, this is Jenny and this is the YRD autocomplete interview
This is the most I had to talk about myself.
Wow
When did Jenny join Blackpink?
I was always there.
We put out our first
single in 2016 August so that's when Blackpink happened
when did Jennie move to New Zealand I was nine and I was there till
14 so five good years see I used to have a stronger accent but it's
completely gone people don't ever guess that I'm from New Zealand anymore which is sad
I think this is a New Zealand thing about me.
I like Marmite jam.
So me and Rosie were the only excited people when we were in a city
and they provide us with Vegemite or Marmite.
When did Jennie release Solo?
Five years ago, I want to say.
Six years ago?
Five years ago?
I think five.
My bet's on five.
It feels like it was such a long time ago because while preparing for Mantra,
I looked back at the videos and photos of me from back in the solo
days.
And I was like, wow, I look so young and cute.
It's definitely different working as a solo artist.
I'm in the studio alone, first of all.
When I was working on the group stuff, I talked a lot with the girls
on if we all agree and relate to the song a lot.
But now I have to make all of those decisions on my own.
So I think that's the biggest difference that I have.
Next, please.
When did Jennie start singing?
Professionally?
14.
But I was singing my whole life.
I'm assuming I was singing as a kid too, so.
Jennie outfits stage.
We like to change around our tour outfits a lot when we're on tour, especially,
because we like to just match the vibe of the city that we're in.
But I feel like my style is pretty open-minded.
Why is Jennie Instagram Jennie Ruby Jane?
It's a name that I came up with when I was in school in New
Zealand.
I wanted a nice, long, pretty name like my friends, and then it just stuck
with me.
So it's like a name for me that I made for myself.
How to dress like Jennie.
I feel like everyone's killing it though.
Like, everyone already knows the answer to this.
Next, please.
I always wanted to do this.
What is Jennie like?
I am a very shy person.
Even when I'm around my friends, I'm likely to be the quiet one.
But I am very different from what you see on stage, so hopefully we get
to know each other better.
What is Jennie's favorite fruit?
It changes all the time, actually.
It used to be strawberries.
Nowadays, I'm really into kiwis.
What is Jennie's favorite song in Blackpink?
This is always a tough one.
I wanna say Lovesick Girls right now.
Like it changes all the time, but right now it's Lovesick Girls.
It has such a cute, girly moments of Blackpink and it's a rare type of
vibe that we have on stage because we do a lot of stronger charismatic things.
So yeah.
What is Jennie, oh, what is Jennie nickname?
I have a lot of nicknames.
I have Jendeukie, that's a Korean nickname.
I have NiNi, my friends call me NiNi.
It evolved from my original name, which is Jennie.
What is Jennie doing now?
Well, I'm currently at the Wired interview, but my single, Mantra, came out a few
days ago, I think.
So I'm very busy being happy.
I think making of this whole album was definitely a big step for me to
grow as a solo artist.
This specific song, Mantra, is I think a great opener.
It's like a little bit of a tease moment of Jennie, I would say, into
the album.
Just Jennie.
Who Jennie Blackpink best friend?
I have lots of best friends.
You guys are my best friends.
How many piercings does Jennie have?
So I used to have a lot of piercings as a teenager but I got
rid of it throughout the years and I think I am left with four piercings
on this year and two on this year.
So just on my ears.
Does Jennie write songs?
Indeed I do!
Yeah, hopefully you guys get to hear more of my songs when the album drops,
so...
Be excited!
Jennie...
Jennie Dog!
Aww, my dog is named Kuma.
He's back home, he's with my mom right now, I miss him.
He's the best behaved dog ever.
He loves me though, I think I'm still up to this day his favorite human
on earth, even though I don't get to see him as much as I did.
But yeah, he's very happy to see me every time I see him.
Final word?
Yay!
Jenny.
Jenny rap.
Yes, I do rap.
Thank you.
I love to rap.
And you'll hear more in my album too.
Jenny, one of the girls.
It is my most streamed song on Spotify.
I'm so happy that it's doing great Jenny Capybara I watched a capybara video
before I got here today I know capybara isn't like the most well-known animals on
earth And I started to talk about them a lot Because I get questions about
what is my favorite animal And I've always been attached to capybara Yeah they probably
just wanted to know what a capybara is but I think they are more trending
nowadays.
Makes me very proud, so.
I shot a music video with one years ago for Ice Cream.
That was one of the best day ever that I had.
I need to go see one soon.
Oh, many Jack Moose runway.
So I walked for the Jack Moose show in May in Capri, It was my
first time running on a runway.
It was a very special occasion for me.
I only have good memories from this day because I thought I'd be very nervous
and anxious about it.
But from the moment I arrived in Capri, I was just like, let me just
have fun.
That was also another proud moment of this year for me.
Thankfully, I wasn't surprised by any of the questions.
I think I had most of them in mind.
So step it up, guys.
Ask more interesting questions to Google about me.
Thank you for having me and I'll see you next time.
Bye.